stand-up comedy man this is uh this is a
tough business
i don't mean a rain on anyone's parade
it's uh
it's hard to make money doing this uh my
financial situation is so bad right now
that i'm being sponsored by a child in
africa
i can't i can't even pay my bills on
time i don't pay my bills on site
if you don't pay your bills on time this
is what happens
a couple weeks later you get another one
in the mail that'll be read
and it'll say something like urgent
please pay immediately
right like just because the bill's red
i'm gonna all of a sudden have the money
to pay for it
it's like relaxed electric provider i
know it's urgent
i'm reading your bill by candlelight
oh i don't know i get insecure about
like the little money that i make like i
got stuck in this conversation recently
with a couple of wealthy people and one
of them asked me how my investments were
doing
i i told them both avocados should be
right by tomorrow
soft man like if i go to a restaurant i
never look at the name of the dish
i just look to see if i could afford it
you know i'm like yes waiter i'll have a
water and a
6.95
a lot of people are coming out with a
book now like like
actors dentists musicians it's it's like
the latest get rich quick scheme
i was at the bookstore the other day and
i saw a book that was titled
how i got rich from selling books
written by an average guy right i bought
the book
took it home opened it up it just read
[Laughter]
thanks
i've watched a lot of these like antique
appraisal shows where people bring their
antiques in
to find out how much that stuff is worth
right and this is what i noticed crowd
that when white people bring antiques in
they're always worth money
and when black people bring antiques in
they're not
like a white person bring antiquing and
the appraiser is like
wow this is an original copy of the bill
of rights
it's worth a fortune and then a black
person will bring antique in
and the appraiser is like wow
this is your grandfather's old heating
bill
it's not worth anything
in fact he owes 80 bucks
the bill's still red you know
i used to work at a warehouse before
doing this i didn't really care for the
job
but like a warehouse job sometimes it
could be like an easier job to get
because you don't need like a lot of
different skills to work at a warehouse
like i remember the day i applied i went
in
i asked the boss where the applications
were he's like they're over there under
that box
i go over there i lift up the box he's
like congratulations you got the job
it was stressful working there so you
wouldn't think like that job would be
stressful
but you know the job is stressful when
just to make it through the day
you start humming negro spirituals
and your white co-workers join in with
you that's
that's how you know
i worked at this uh the shipping
warehouse and we had to be careful
because the penalty for shipping
hazardous material
without the proper paperwork was 250 000
or up to 10 years in prison
10 years in prison it's got to be really
embarrassing
being the guy going to prison for that
you know he gets there and cellmate's
like so how long in here for
he's like 10 years what'd you do
i shipped a gallon of paint without a
hazmat sticker
cellmate's like you too
you